A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Series A FA310
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence - Green, L. G. - Guzman (Box 13, Folder 94)
  Green, Lawrence G., January 20, 1927. Visit.Green, Rosamond E., 1924 - 1931. Best wishes, visits.Green, S. D., June 1927. Autograph declined.Greene, Laura L., July 1924. Sends photographs.Greenville Methodist Church, 1920 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller gifts. Lakewood, New Jersey.Gregg, Frank M., November 1921. Would restore Plymouth, Massachusetts.Gregory, George H., November 10, 1931. Sending cut glass piece.Grimes, Frank, April 6, 1931. Tells of John D. Rockefeller horses in 1888.Grimm, Miss Litta, 1921 - 1930. Vocalist at church. Best wishes. Visits. Gifts.Greswald, William E., (Mr. and Mrs.), October 1926. Musicale invitation.Grouard, Elizabeth P., November 1922. Visit.Grube, C. H., August 22, 1921. Church appeal.Guffey, James M., 1925 - 1926; 1929. His view of the early history of the Standard Oil company and oil fields.Guhl, (Mrs.), January 8, 1928. Has received picture of gardens.Gumbel, Amelia, 1928 - 1930. Dimes.Gunnell, Gertrude, February 1, 1927. Sends picture.Guzman, Carlos V., December 7, 1923. Greetings from the Philippines.
- Correspondence - Haber, M. E. - Hale, W. A. (Box 13, Folder 95)
  Haber, Mary E., September 1925. Wedding gift.Hacker, John C., 1924 - 1925. Personal appeal.Hadden, Alexander, August - September 1920. Early Settlers Association.Haddix, S. K., November 11, 1922. Personal appeal.Hadley, W. L., July 1925. Hoped for golf date.Haffner, John, July 1922. Birthday wishes.Hagar, Frederick W., October - November 1923. Condolence, Church appeal.Hagen, Walter, February 1927. Sends golf balls.Hagerty, W. J., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1923 - 1931. Cleveland friends, personal appeal, church problems.Haines, Mary, February 20, 1930. Golf.Hair, Thomas J. (Mrs.), May 1928. University of Chicago chapel.Hale, William A., January 1926. Marriage announcement.
- Correspondence - Halifax Council - Halifax YMCA (Box 13, Folder 96)
  Halifax Council, Boy Scouts of America, 1926 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller gifts.Halifax Garden Club, March 10, 1929. Visited gardens.Halifax Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1924 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller gifts.
- Correspondence - Hall, B. - Hance (Box 13, Folder 97)
  Hall, Bolton, July 1928. Appeal.Hall, Charles, September 25, 1931. Anniversary of first job.Hall, Miss Charlotte C., 1920 - 1924. Appeals for Loyal Legion Temperance Society. Visits. Indian welfare.Hall, Fred J., 1920 - 1926. Golf, condolences.Hall, Helen B., (Mrs.), October 1925. Questions about J. S. Sargent.Hall, Henry M., 1924 - 1925. Cleveland memories.Hall, Margaret M., 1926 - 1931. Sends poems, (same as Kykuit).Halle, Louis J., October 1927. Autograph.Hamilton, Charles A., February - March 1929. Golf balls.Hamilton, Frank A., February 1929. Church appeal.Hamilton, Mary S., 1920 - 1927. Gifts.Hammond, John Hays, March 16, 1929. Re: Stewart.Hammond, John Henry, (Mr. and Mrs.), February - March 1927. Wedding announcement.Hammond, Natalie H., March 20, 1929. Thanks for poem.Hance, Irwin H., October 2, 1929. Condolence.Hance, John A., 1920 - 1930. Best wishes.
- Correspondence - Hanley - Harris (Box 13, Folder 98)
  Hanley, Elijah A., March 16, 1926. Condolence.Hanna, Arrial, February - March 1923. Appeal.Hanna, H. M., February 14, 1921. Condolence.Hanna, Helen, (married name Bullis), October 15, 1930. Visit.Hanna, Marcus A., (Mrs.), November 18, 1921. Condolence.Hanna, R. J., October 15, 1930. Visit.Hanna, Virginia, (Mrs. R. J.), March 1927. Sends fruit.Hannah, John, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1920 - 1922; 1925. Treatment of older employees on the estate.Hansen, Augusta, (Mrs.), December 1921. Sends pillow.Hanson, Henry R., May 1929. Church appeal.Hardesty, Walter C., December 1924. Invitation.Hardin, Earl U., December 13, 1928. Golf program.Harding, Earl, (Louise G.), (Mr. and Mrs.), 1930 - 1931. Photograph sent.Harding, President and Mrs. Warren G., 1921 - 1923. Thanks for Mr. Teagle, condolence.Hargreaves, M. H., (Mrs.), 1919 - 1930. Housekeeper at Abeyton Lodge, personal wishes.Harkness, Edward S., 1926. Condolence.Harkness, William L., (Mrs.), June 1922. Wedding invitation.Harmon, Leslie, 1927. Claimed relationship.Harms, C. F., 1921 - 1923. Visit, Standard Oil memories.Harper, E. L., July - August 1920. Job applicant.Harper, Nita, 1923. Personal appeal.Harper, Samuel, N., 1920; 1928 - 1929. Son of William R. Harper, news of family.Harper, William R., 1927 - 1928. Proposed memorial, F. T. Gates comments, news of Harper family.Harris, Albert, February 20, 1929. Visit.Harris, Arthur M., 1920; 1924; 1929 - 1931. Baptist leader, ministers' pensions.Harris, Jennie G., 1927 - 1930. Sends golf tees, best wishes.
- Correspondence - Harrison - Hatch, Henry (Mrs.) (Box 13, Folder 99)
  Harrison, Duncan B., October 31, 1929. Sends poem.Hart, Frank J., 1920 - 1921; 1925. Employee, gifts.Hart, George L., 1929 - 1930. Early investment in Standard Oil.Hart, Malcolm, 1924 - 1927; 1930. Job applicant, family friend, best wishes, visits.Hartley, Mrs. Richard, 1917 - 1919; 1928. John D. Rockefeller gifts.Harvard University, 1925; 1930. Invitations.Harvey, Ashton, 1922 - 1924. Died during golf game with John D. Rockefeller. John D. Rockefeller's assistance.Harvey, George, 1920 - 1928. Editor, Ambassador to London, comments on Harding and Coolidge.Harwood, Paul H., (Mr. and Mrs.), June 1931. Wedding announcement.Haserot, Francis H., June 30, 1921. Separates himself from criticism of John D. Rockefeller.Haskell, Coburn, (Mrs.), 1923; 1926; 1931. Invitation.Hastings, W. H., January 12, 1929. Sending dimes.Hatch, Henry, (Mrs.), April - May 1926. Wedding gift.
- Correspondence - Hatch, Mary A. (Mrs.) - Henthorne (Box 14, Folder 100)
  Hatch, Mary A., (Mrs.), 1919 - 1924. Visits, nickels, dimes, gifts.Hawks, B. M., 1923 - 1930. Worked for William Rockefeller, sends fruit.Hawley, Alice M., January 18, 1926. Christmas wishes. Hawley, Fred S., July 1924. Sends clipping.Hawley, Miriamo, (Mrs.), October 1929. Wedding invitation.Hayes, J. W., 1929 - 1930. Sends dime.Hayne, Coe, 1923; 1926 - 1930. Personal gifts, Pocantico Union Church.Heaney, F. J. October 1919. Pocantico priest, farewell.Hearne, Clara S., 1926. Dime.Heaton, James, October 1929. Helen Pugh pianist.Heckle, Emma, 1925; 1929 - 1931. Best wishes.Heckman, Lillie, (Wallace), (Mrs.), April 15, 1927. Condolence.Hedstrom, Arthur E., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1924; 1929. Condolence, gifts, wedding invitation.Hefterman, Rabbi A., July 15, 1930. Sends book.Heil, Charles A., (Buelah E.), (Mr. and Mrs.), September 1929. Visit.Helbing, Clara C., May 28, 1930. Thanks for General Education Board.Helmus, Peter, August - September 1926. Watchman, condolence.Helsel, Ruth E., August 10, 1927. Visit.Henderson, Honorah, M. T., June 1931. Wedding invitation.Henderson, J. M., (Mr. and Mrs.), June 1922. Cleveland friends, Golden wedding.Hendrington, C. F., February, September 1926. Best wishes.Henry, Hazel, October 7, 1929. Visit.Henry, Symons & Company, April 1925. Tapestry for sale.Henthorne, Dorothy, (Mrs.), April - June 1928. Personal gifts.
- Correspondence - Hepburn - Hill (Box 14, Folder 101)
  Hepburn, Emily, (Barton), (Mrs.), 1922 - 1923. Condolence.Hepner, William, September 1927. Best wishes.Herman, Elizabeth, (Mrs.), November 24, 1924. Best wishes.Herman, John A., 1927 - 1929. Friendly comments.Herrick, Myron T., 1927; 1929. Birthday wishes, condolences.Hesel, William, October 5, 1927. Dime.Hesnault, Mary C., (Mrs.), July - August 1929. Sends spectacles for sale, returned.Heustis, J. W., (Bertha L.), (Mrs.), January 4, 1928. Church soloist, 1892, memories.Hewitt, C. J., July 1924. Re: Father a classmate of John D. Rockefeller.Hibbard, Harriet L., June 26, 1927. Personal appeal.Hicks, Amanda M., July 1922. Best wishes.Higgins, C. M., 1926; 1929. Christmas wishes, memories of Standard Oil.Higgins, Lucy A., March 6, 1925. Visit.Higgs, William J., November 10, 1930. Photograph.Hilger, Marie, (Mrs.), 1931. Photographs of John D. Rockefeller, personal appeal.Hill, Albert, 1925 - 1926. Dime, visit.Hill, Blanche, 1929; 1931. Condolence, memorial to husband, (Albert Hill).Hill, Cora R., (Mrs.), 1920 - 1922; 1929. Church soprano, personal appeals.Hill, Edmund C., January - February 1930. Interview.Hill, Ira J. B., April 22, 1931. Circuit riding minister, New Jersey.
- Correspondence - Hinsdale, Katherine, 1920-1925 (Box 14, Folder 102)
  Lakewood friend. Personal gifts.
- Correspondence - Hinsdale, Katherine, 1926-1929 (Box 14, Folder 103)
- Correspondence - Hoagland - Hopson (Box 14, Folder 104)
  Hoagland, Henry and Rose, 1929 - 1930. Personal Gifts. Harford Mills.Hobbie, E. F., 1925; 1928 - 1932. Daughter of Andrew Freese of Cleveland, best wishes.Hodgdon, Thomas and Jennie, December 1929. Visit.Hodges, J. O., 1921; 1925. Best wishes.Hodgkins, Louise M., (Mrs.), August 1928. Gratitude for John D. Rockefeller's education gifts.Hoff, Francis L., April 1926. Appeal.Hofius, Ellie, March 1930. Chiropractor.Hogan, John F., November - December 1921. Defended John D. Rockefeller in magazine, appeal.Hogan, John J., 1922 - 1924. Optometrist.Hoggard, Robert, September 6, 1928. Visit.Hohing, Adelaide L., 1923 - 1928. Greetings, condolences.Hohl, George M., January 1929. Greetings.Hoit, Alice M., April 1927. Wedding announcement.Holliday, W. T., 1928 - 1929. Standard Oil of Ohio, Visit, Comments on oil industry.Hollingsworth, Emma J., (Mrs.), June 1926. Thanks for gift to church.Hollingsworth, Henry S., March 1919. Claimed to have created first filling station.Holmes, Robert S., 1930 - 1931. Sends poems.Holt, Hamilton, April 6, 1931. Visit.Holt, Thomas G., 1927 - 1928. Sends medicine.Honest Ballot Association, 1920 - 1921. Contributions.Hooker, Margaret T., October 14, 1921 Vassar Fund Drive.Hooper, Eleanor B., November 1926. Wedding announcement.Hooper, L. F., (Mrs.), October 1921. F. T. Gates daughter wedding gift.Hoover, Herbert, November 1928. Congratulations.Hopson, Mary, 1920; 1923. Photographer, copies of Sargent portrait.
- Correspondence - Horner - Hughes (Box 14, Folder 105)
  Horner, N. L., (Mrs.), January 1, 1928. Florida hotel.Hoster, William, 1922; 1927. Asks for photograph, Interviewed John D. Rockefeller in France in 1905.Hotchkiss, Kate M, December 31, 1931. Remembers 5th Avenue Baptist church days.House, Roy T., November - December 1930. Sends German play about John D. Rockefeller by Friedrich Wolf.Houser, Charles D., 1925 - 1930. Euclid Avenue Church news.Houston, Ada, February 27, 1930. Remembers Georgia visit in 1905.Houston, Tacie B., October 1923. Wedding gift.Howard, Albert S., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1929. Letter of introduction.Howard, Clarence H., February 27, 1925. Tribute to John D. Rockefeller.Howard, John C., February 1931. Visit.Howatt, D. E., 1928. Best wishes.Howe, E. W., 1921 - 1924. Kansas editor.Howe, Margaret, 1923. Thanks for card.Howell, Connie, L., April 30, 1930. Dimes.Hoyt, Colgate, 1919 - 1922. Visits, family, condolence.Hoyt, F. H., 1924; 1930. Worked 40 years for Standard Oil company.Hoyt, John S., (Mr. and Mrs.), May 1927. Wedding invitation.Huang, Tien Lai, 1929 - 1930. Interview.Hudson, A. P., (Mrs.), April - May 1919. Request for information on prohibition.Hudson, Carles F., July 1926. Appeal.Huey, H. G., April 1926. Visit.Hughes, Adella P., 1920; 1927. Cleveland music teacher, appeal, managed Cleveland Orchestra, visit.Huges, J. Warren, 1921 - 1931. Priest, personal gifts.
- Correspondence - Hulburt - Hyde, Jabez V. D. (Box 14, Folder 106)
  Hulburt, D. W., August 1924. Why John D. Rockefeller goes to church.Humphreys, O. H., January 1931. Sends book.Hungerford, U. T., July 1922. Pass to visit Pocantico.Hunie, J. H., (Mrs.), June 1926. Thanks for gift to Euclid church.Himlom. William J., (Mr. and Mrs.), October 1929. Wedding announcement.Hunt, Edward L., August 1927. Remembers visits to John D. Rockefeller's home.Hunt, Edward P., November 1923. Condolence.Hunt, Horace H., 1929 - 1931. Minister, Tarrytown.Hunt, R., (Mrs.), 1929. Acknowledgement.Hunt, Seth B., 1927; 1931. Wedding gifts.Hunter, Burtis C., July 23, 1923. Thank you for gift.Hunter, Robert C., 1927 - 1931. Insurance man. Sent gifts.Huron Road Hospital, 1926; 1930. Appeals for homeopathic hospital.Husted, Viola, (Mrs.), 1920; 1922. Appeals.Hutchins, H. C., January 31, 1928. Sends apples.Huver, Elsie, (Mrs.), May 24, 1921. Personal gift.Hyde, Jabez V. D., February 1927. Sends golf diary.
- Correspondence - Hyde, J. Chester - Hyde, Marie (Box 14, Folder 107)
  Hyde, J. Chester, 1918 - 1931. Retired African missionary, news of missions, family, sale of oil in Congo.Hyde, Marie A., 1921; 1926 - 1930. Memories.
- Correspondence - (I) (Box 15, Folder 108)
  Idlewild Fruit Company, May - July 1925. Sale.Inglis, W. O., 1921 - 1931. Birthday wishes. Report on oil men. Interview in 1921.Ingram, Emma S., February 13, 1931. Visit.Innis, William S., (Mr. and Mrs.), April 1921. Marriage announcement.Inscho, G. S., (Mrs.), 1921; 1931. Visits.Institution of Mercy, July 18, 1926. Asks for automobile.Irish, W. M., 1926 - 1928. Visit.Irons, Henry Clay, 1919 - 1925. Gifts, visits.Isley, Lily E., (Mrs.), and Velma, Rolanda, and Marsha. 1928 - 1931. Lakewood widow. Plans. Personal gifts.
- Correspondence - Jackson - Johnson, Clare P. (Box 15, Folder 109)
  Jackson, Arthur C., July 1930. Longfellow association.Jackson, Audrey, 1930. Golf.Jacksonville Kiwanis Club, January 1930. Best wishes.Jacobs, Arono, February 1923. Concert.Jacobson, A. W., (Mrs.), 1929. Dimes.James, Joe F., (Mrs.), April 18, 1927. Lookalikes.James, P. W., February 1923. Golf.James, Walter B., (Mrs.), 1920; 1923; 1927. Gift. Condolence.Jamieson, Burton L., January 16, 1928. Autograph.Jamieson, Euphemia L., June - July 1921. House hunting.Jamison, Martha, 1920 - 1925. Sends gift to John D. Rockefeller. Visits.Janis, Elsie, July 1929. Offering Philipse Manor for sale with booklet.Jarratt, C. D., August 1928. Tribute to John D. Rockefeller.Jefferson, Charles E., June 1925. Golf.Jenkins, C. M., February 1922. Sends cane.Jenkins, D. J., December 1927. Orphanage appeal.Jenkins, J. Alva, 1921. Old employee, needs help, not given.Jenks, Benjamin, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1924 - 1925. Wedding gift for daughter.Jennings, Annie B., (Mrs.), 1925 - 1927. Visits.Jennings, Constance, 1927. Wedding gift.Jennings, Mary R., May 1927. Condolence.Jennings, Philip B., (Mr. and Mrs.), May 1921. Wedding invitation.Jennison, Frank J., December 1929. Interview.Jeter, Nancy E., (Mrs.), July 14, 1931. Personal appeal, named baby John D.Jochimsen, Editha, April 1930. Sends pictures. Johnson, C. H., (Mr. and Mrs.), May 1922. Wedding announcement.Johnson, C. R., September - October 1929. Claims "Rockefeller-Archibald" owed him money.Johnson, C. Oscar, October 4, 1927. Appreciation for John D. Rockefeller good work.Johnson, Caroline, March 19, 1931. Met John D. Rockefeller, Her husband wrote words to "When You and I Were Young, Maggie".Johnson, Clare P., 1920 - 1927. Friend, visit.
- Correspondence - Johnson, Elias M., 1920-1923 (Box 15, Folder 110)
  Visits, golf.
- Correspondence - Johnson, Elias M., 1924-1931 (Box 15, Folder 111)
- Correspondence - Johnson, Emory L. - Jones, Grace (Box 15, Folder 112)
  Johnson, Emory L., 1924; 1929. Golf.Johnson, Etta M., November 1927. Photograph.Johnson, George F., 1929 - 1930. Sends golf balls.Johnson, Guy, (Mr. and Mrs.), and daughter Helen R. Johnson. 1922 - 1931. Relative, husband illness and death, gifts.Johnson, Herbert S., Jr., 1926; 1931. Dimes, sermons.Johnson, Jennie, (Mrs.), May 1919. Personal gift.Johnson, Jessie P., (Mrs.), January 24, 1929. Personal appeal.Johnson, Karl G., October 1924. Job with Standard Oil Marine division.Johnson, Martha A., 1931. Visit.Johnson, Nettie L., 1919 - 1922. Personal gifts.Johnson, Robert U., July 1930. Appeal.Johnson, Walter, 1927 - 1928. Photographer.Johnson, Willas F., April 1929. Permission to use John D. Rockefeller letters in a biography of Colonial Harvey.Johnston, George B., October 15, 1930. Asks for information about oil country.Johnston, George R., December 18, 1929. Miniature golf.Johnston, Loren R., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1924 - 1929. Hotel manager in Ormond Beach, motion pictures. Condolence.Johnston, Mary C., (Mrs.), (Rufus P.), 1924 - 1931. Visit, minister's wife, best wishes.Johnston, Mary E., (Mrs.), February 1926. Personal appeal.Jones, C. Bion, (Mr.), January 1925. Father a messenger at 26 Broadway.Jones, Darwin G., 1922 - 1926. Cleveland memories, Birthday wishes.Jones, Francis M., August 10, 1924. Visit.Jones, George H., (Mrs.), 1928 - 1929. Death, condolence.Jones, Grace A., (Mrs.), November 18, 1926. John D. Rockefeller gives rectory some trees.
- Correspondence - Jones, John D. - Julian (Box 15, Folder 113)
  Jones, Chaplain John D., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1920 - 1926. Floating Bethel Mission, Cleveland. Gifts. Condolence.Jones, Mary, February 4, 1929. Church appeal.Jones, S. A., January 24, 1931. Florida ship canal.Jordon, Isabella S., (Mrs.), 1921 - 1923; 1930. Memories of Augusta visits.Joslyn, Mary, (Mrs.), 1921 - 1922. Personal gifts.Joyce, Adrian D., (Mr. and Mrs.), October 1930. Wedding announcement.Joyner, J. J., July - August 1928. Mexican church appeal.Judd, Bertha G., (Mrs.), (Orin R.), September 22, 1927. Visit.Judd, Edward W., August 1931. Job applicant.Judd, Mary E., (Mrs.), 1920; 1924. Wedding gift, best wishes.Judson, Henry Pratt, 1920 - 1922. University of Chicago news. Summary of his activities as President.Julian, (Brother), July 7, 1929. Birthday wishes.
- Correspondence - Kahn - Kifer (Box 15, Folder 114)
  Kahn, (Mr. and Mrs.), February 1928. Wedding announcement.Kaim, Lawrence E., 1923 - 1929. Best wishes.Kane, Elizabeth C., January 23, 1927. Visit.Kaohelelani, Princess, July 9, 1930. Hawaiian.Karel, Emma, September 2, 1930. Has story to sell.Kay, James I., 1920 - 1921. Visit.Kearney, Catherine A., 1918 - 1925. Visit, best wishes.Kearney, Margaret, 1926 - 1927. Condolence.Keebler, Philip F., 1928. Refund on income tax. Birth announcement.Keeler, Harney R., (Mrs.), 1928; 1930. Church appeal, marriage announcement.Keeler, Elizabeth, (Mrs.), Wendell A., 1928 - 1931. Wedding gift, best wishes.Keelips, Robert W., 1918 - 1920; 1925; 1930. Former secretary, Seat on Stock Exchange, 1918 comments on Alta House.Keith, Dorothy M., (Mrs.), 1921; 1927. Visit.Keith, James B., October 1930. Rockefeller Tag Day.Kelley, John H., 1931. Council Bluffs, Iowa, employee.Kelly, Anna L,. 1920 - 1923. Abby Aldrich Rockefeller's secretary, small gifts.Kelsey, Frederick W., 1921; 1931. Visit to grounds.Kendall, Hayward, 1928. Sends articles he has written, condolences.Kennedy, Mary T., September 29, 1925. Dime.Kerr, Janet B., (Mrs.), (Clarence), June 22, 1929. Visit.Ketchum, Jane M., (Mrs.), July 27, 1929. Visit.Kharum, M., January 1930. Dime.Kiefer, D. W., September 19, 1930. Lot for sale.Kifer, Eugene, 1921 - 1924. Employee, gift.
- Correspondence - Kimbrough - Koehler (Box 16, Folder 115)
  Kimbrough, I. N., January 3, 1930. Thanks for good work.King, John H., (Mr. and Mrs.), September 1931. Wedding announcement.King, W. L. Mackenzie, 1921; 1923. Christmas wishes, visit.Kingley, Betty, (Mrs., Joseph), June 1930. Took snapshot of John D. Rockefeller.Kinmonth, Lillian H., April 21, 1930. Dime.Kinsley, Elizabeth H., (Mrs. Harold S.), October 15, 1930. Visit.Kirby, Fred M., 1921; 1924. Florida friend, visits.Kirk, W. P., June 8, 1921. John D. Rockefeller gave him road directions.Kite, Cecil, July 15, 1929. Visit.Kline, Effie P., (Mrs.), (Virgil P.), April 1923. Sends photograph.Knapp, A. J., 1920 - 1926; 1931. Employee, Best wishes, reference for college.Knickerbacker, John, November 6, 1929. Support for 18th Amendment.Knight, George L., September 18, 1928. Five dollar gift.Knight, Hilda, July 13, 1927. Thanks.Knorpp, Wesley, July 1931. Birthday editorial.Knowles, Winifred R. G., (Mrs.), October 9, 1929. Appeal.Knox, John B., 1921. Visit, birthday wishes.Koehler, Lisbet, (Mrs.), 1921 - 1924, 1930. Gifts, pianist.
- Correspondence - Kolb, John C. and Mrs. Kolb, 1913-1931 (Box 16, Folder 116)
  Christmas greetings and letters (set of Christmas cards).
- Correspondence - Koshiba - Kuhlow (Box 16, Folder 117)
  Koshiba, H. T., November 30, 1928. Photographs.Kountz, Clark, August 28, 1925. Visit.Kraft, Hubert F., 1927; 1928. Visits.Krug, Ernest F., Dr., 1919 - 1923; 1929 - 1930. Visit, optometrist.Kuhlow, Ernest J., April - May 1920. Chiropractor.
- Correspondence (Lad-Lak) (Box 16, Folder 118)
  Ladies Aid Society, Greenville M. E. Church, September 26, 1919. Subscription.Lagerbery, Guy de, September 27, 1923. Best wishes.Laidlaw, Robert W., July 1930. Marriage announcement.Laidlaw, Walter, 1924, 1929. Golf, religious work in New York City.Laird, Nellie W., (Mrs.), 1921 - 1922. Gift, family problems.Lakeview Cemetery, 1921 - 1922. John D. Rockefeller resignation from Board.Lakewood Engineering Company, October 15, 1921. To the Stockholders.Lakewood Farm Inn, Inc., September 1920. Photographs.Lakewood, New Jersey, Organizations, John D. Rockefeller contributions: Boy Scouts, 1929; District Nurse Association, 1921, 1928, 1931; Firemen's Association, 1930; First Aid Squad, 1930; First Baptist Church, 1919 - 1931; World's War Memorial Committee, 1922.
- Correspondence - Lakewood, New Jersey - Organizations (Box 16, Folder 119)
  Lakewood Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1918-1930. John D. Rockefeller contributions.Lakewood Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA), 1918-1931. John D. Rockefeller contributions.
- Correspondence - Lamb, E. B. - Laurance, M. B. (Box 16, Folder 120)
  Lamb, E. B., May 17, 1921. Best wishes.Lamb, Janie Brockenbrough, (Mrs.), July 1924. Birthday wishes.Lamberty, Mary S., 1919 - 1931. Pensioner.La Monte, Charles L., 1922 - 1931. Childhood friend, aging, poem by Mark Twain on tainted money. Mrs. Life.Lamey, Helen G., (Mrs. Charles), 1922; 1925. Visit.Landers, Kathryn, July 12, 1921. Gift.Lang, Charles F., October 1926. John D. Rockefeller investment in Lakewood Engineering company.Langer, Charles F., 1924 - 1927. News photos.Larkin, John, 1923; 1929. Best wishes.Larson, M. June - July 1926. Church appeal.Laurance, Mary B., (Mrs.), 1926 - 1927. Visit.
- Correspondence - Law, H. H. - Lennon (Box 16, Folder 121)
  Law, Henry H., August 9, 1920. Visit.Law, M. A., September 23, 1919. Sends art work.Laws, Lafayette L., March 1931. Negro school appeal.Lawson, Alfred W., 1927 - 1928. Plans for 100 passenger plane.Lawson, B. Robert, May 9, 1925. Gift of shrubbery to church.Lawson, Theodosia, (Mrs.), August 1922. Best wishes.Lay, Charles H., March 29, 1928. Visit.Lay, Russell C., (Mr. and Mrs.), September 1927. Wedding invitation.Lebanon Valley College, April 22, 1930. Thanks for General Education Board gift.Ledbetter, C. M., 1922 - 1925. Ivy Lee's uncle, sends nuts, praise for John D. Rockefeller.Lederer, Sam, May 23, 1930. John D. Rockefeller's cousin in Chicago, William Avery.Ledyard, Lewis C., (Mr. and Mrs.), October 1928. Wedding invitation.Lee, Ivy L., 1924 - 1930. Publicity for John D. Rockefeller. Sends books, clippings. Asks him to sign photos for other people. Marriage of daughter, Alice to Chandler Cuddlipp.Lee, Marion, (Mrs.), May 1926. Church appeal.Leet, Kline F., February 26, 1920. Please return to Cleveland.Leggett, M. B., (Mrs.), 1920 - 1926. Pensioner.Leigh, Itura R., March 2, 1921. Church appeal.Leland, Matilda C., (Mrs.), 1920; 1930. Personal gifts.Lenihan, Ernest, (Mr. and Mrs.), May 1927. Wedding announcement.Lennon, Reverend Patrick J., 1919 - 1930. Visits, golf, wishes.
- Correspondence - Lent, F. - Life (Box 16, Folder 122)